all righty guys welcome back to another video and these next I want to say like
所有用右手球员欢迎回到 另一个 视频和这些我想说的 就好
five to ten videos they're going to be the coolest place on tutorials so far
他们将会有 五到十个视频 教程 上最酷的地方 至今
because I'm going to show you guys how to use this awesome
因为我要告诉你们 怎么样 使用这个真棒
library it's actually really easy to use but you can do awesome things to images
库它实际上非常 容易 使用 但你可以 为图像 做很棒的事情
like rotate them stretch them resize them you can actually make some really
喜欢旋转它们拉伸它们调整大小 他们你真的可以做一些
awesome photo filters like you would in Photoshop or Instagram so I'm gonna be
像你一样的真棒照片滤镜 Photoshop或Instagram所以我会
showing you guys all of that so uh well let's go ahead and get started
向 你们 展示 所有这些呃 好吧 让我们开始吧
oh now freakin whooping-cough already actually winter just started we just got
哦， 现在吓得咳嗽已经咳嗽了 实际上冬天 刚刚开始我们刚刚 开始
the first snowfall and for some reason whenever the snow starts falling the
第一场降雪 ，出于某种原因 每当雪花开始 下降 的
inside of my house gets really dry like my skin starts drying out but that's
在我家里面变得非常干燥 我的皮肤开始变干，但 就是这样
disgusting so let's get back on track here now obviously I'm going to be
恶心，让我们回到正轨 现在在这里很明显，我将 是
teaching you guys how to edit images do some cool things with them so we
教你们 如何编辑 图像呢 与他们一些很酷的事情，所以我们
probably need some images now I already took a couple from my computer we should
可能现在需要一些图片，我 已经 我们应该从我的电脑上拿走一对
show them to you guys here's me is baby I'm also going to be using this one this
向你们展示给我们这里的我是宝贝 我也将 使用这一个本
is my old profile picture for Bucky's room
是我对Bucky's的旧图片 房间
this girl ping I just made this in Photoshop real quick um I don't know why
这个女孩我刚刚做了这个 Photoshop真的很快嗯我不知道为什么
I chose this I thought it was kind of funny she looks like I don't even know
我选择了这个，我认为它有点像 有趣她看起来我甚至都不知道
she looks like but I needed something with some colors and the last photo I'm
她看起来像 我需要的 东西 我有一些颜色和最后一张照片
going to be using is a picture of my sister and I so of course just go ahead
将要使用的是我的照片 姐姐和我当然 要继续吧
and grab any picture or image from your computer and drag in the same directory
并抓住你的任何图片或图像 计算机并拖动 到同一目录中
is your Python file and you're going to be good but if for some reason you want
是你的Python文件，你要去 好，但如果由于某种原因你想要
to use my pictures then I'll post them on the forum but you know you probably
使用我的照片然后我会发布它们 在论坛上，但你可能知道
don't want to look at me throughout the whole series so again go get any pictures drop them in and you'll be good
我不想整个看着我 整个系列 所以再次得到任何 图片放入他们，你会很好
to go so now that we have some pictures to work with the only other thing that
去 所以现在我们有 一些照片 与其他唯一的事情一起工作
we need to do kind of to prepare is download that library now if you go to
我们需要做 一些准备就是 如果你去，现在下载该库
file settings of course you can see all your libraries the package is called
当然 ，文件中的设置，你可以看到所有 您的库调用包
pillow so whenever you of course download it click this type in pillow
枕头，所以当然你 下载它在枕头中单击此类型
and you'll be good to go so again that's pillow but check this out
你会很高兴再去那个 枕头， 但检查出来
whenever we actually import the library what we're going to do is we're going to
每当我们实际导入库时 我们要做的就是我们要做的
type from PIL import the class image all right so we're going to be using this
从PIL类型导入所有类图像 对，所以我们 将使用它
image class first but wait a minute buggy you just will need to download the pillow library but right here I'm
图像类首先但等一下 越野车， 你只 需要 下载 枕头图书馆， 但就在这里，我
importing from pill so what the heck is up with that why is it called pill well
从药丸进口所以到底是什么 这就是为什么它 被称为丸 好
if this is probably pretty boring but I just want to explain to you guys what's
如果这可能很无聊 但我 只是想向 你们 解释一下是 什么
going on so you aren't confused right now we're using Python 3.4 this isn't
继续这样你就不会混淆吧 现在我们正在使用Python 3.4 这不是
actually code I'll just type it out real quick so we're using Python 3.4 and the
实际上代码我只是输入真实的 快， 所以我们使用Python 3.4和
library to edit images is called pillow now in the old version of Python that
库编辑图像称为枕头 现在在旧版本的Python中
isn't compatible with what I'm teaching you guys the old version was called pill
与我所教的不相容 你们 老版本被称为丸
so what they did for the new version is they pretty much copied it made it
所以他们为新版本所做的是 他们几乎抄袭了它
compatible with three point four and named the pillow so why didn't they just put pillow right there well for all the
兼容三点四和 命名 枕头 ，为什么他们不这样做 所有的枕头都放在那里
pretty much programmers who wanted who are already familiar with the syntax of
几乎 是那些想要谁的程序员 已经熟悉 的语法了
this library they wanted to you know make it kind of convention familiar for
他们想让 你知道 这个图书馆 让它变得 熟悉
them so that's why they just imported it from pill and you know so I don't know
这就是为什么他们只是进口它 从丸 ，你知道，所以我 不 知道
it's a pretty stupid story but um that's why it's called pill instead of pillow
这是一个非常愚蠢的故事，但是那是 为什么它被称为药丸而不是枕头
to make it kind of compatible and comfortable for all the people who are
使它兼容并且 舒适的所有谁是人
familiar with using it so cool story bro I know but uh whatever so now that we
熟悉使用 它如此酷的故事兄弟 我知道，但 不管我们现在怎么样
got everything taken care of let's go ahead and get started making a basic
得到了 一切照顾 我们走了 提前开始做 一个基本的
image so the first thing we need to do is create some kind of object from this
图像所以我们需要做的第一件事 是从这里创造某种对象
image class a pillow object so I'm just going to name my object IMG it's the
图像类枕头对象所以我只是 要 命名我的对象IMG它的
most boring thing I possibly could have thunk of this sinc funk think think it
我可能有的最无聊的事情 这个sinc funk的一大堆 想想吧
of yep that's it think it up alright so in order to create an object image dot
是的，它认为这样就好了 为了创建一个对象图像点
open and in this open function what you do is you just type the name of what do
打开并在这个 开放的功能 你 是什么 你只需输入 所做的名称即可
I want to use all right so I'll take this image from my computer Bucky jpg
我想用没事 ，所以我就买 这张图片来自 我的电脑Bucky jpg
and what we're saying is pretty much openness
而我们所说的几乎就是这样 透明度
and convert it to a pillow object so now this IMG variable is actually a pillow object so now we can do a bunch of cool
现在将它转换为枕头对象 这个IMG变量实际上是一个枕头 对象所以现在我们可以做一堆酷
things with it before I start showing you guys the really advanced functions of how to manipulate it I'll just show
在我开始展示之前用它做的事情 你们真的很高级的功能 我将 展示如何操纵它
you guys a couple boring stuff first but it's actually
你们两个人 首先是无聊的东西，但事实上
slept we're going to be using a lot so the first thing is just to print out
睡觉我们将会使用很多 第一件事就是打印出来
some properties of this object or the image so we can print out the image size
这个 对象的一些属性 或 图像，所以我们可以打印出图像大小
and the dot symbol and then size property or attribute so actually you
和点符号然后大小 属性或属性所以实际上你
run this right now and you see your returns a tuple of 400 by 400 that of
现在就跑吧，你 看到 你的 返回400乘以400 的元组
course means that this image is 400 by wide by 400 wide by 400 tall and we can
当然意味着这个图像是400 宽400宽400高，我们可以
also print out something like I don't know it's another thing format is
还打印出我不喜欢的东西 知道格式 是 另一回事
another property and what this does is it says okay so right now we can see
另一个属性， 这是做什么的 它说没关系，现在我们可以看到
that it's a JPEG and later on I'm going to be showing you guys how to convert for example if we you wanted to convert
它是一个 JPEG，后来我要去 向你们展示如何转换 例如，如果我们想要转换
this JPEG to a ping or a gif I'm going to be showing you guys how to do that as
这个JPEG到ping或gif我要去 向你们展示如何做到这一点
well but right now this is how you print out simple properties of it and one cool
好吧， 但现在这 是你打印的方式 它的简单属性和一个很酷
thing that I also want to show you guys is this anytime you want to actually
我也想告诉你 事情 的家伙 这是任何时候 你想 实际
display this image then what you can do is you can type the name of the object
显示此图像然后您可以做什么 是您可以键入 对象 的名称
and show now I want to explain one thing down here
现在显示 我想解释一 件事 在这里
you can't display images this is just a console it's pretty much like a fancy command line built just for PyCharm it
你无法显示这只是一个图像 控制台它非常像一个幻想 为 PyCharm 构建的命令行 吧
isn't made to display images itself so whenever you want to display an image on
不是为了显示 图像本身 每当你要 显示的 图像
your computer what happens whenever you call this function is it goes to the
你的电脑 什么时候发生 什么 打电话给这个功能是不是去了
default program that you whenever you you know you're just um put on show you guys
默认程序，无论何时你 你知道你只是把它给你看 人
whenever you're just looking at files like this and you double click
无论何时你只是看文件 像这样，你双击
whenever you double click an image file however it opens is the default image
双击图像文件时 但它打开是默认图像
processing program for your computer now since I have Photoshop installed on my
现在为您的计算机处理程序 因为我已经安装了Photoshop
computer whenever I run this the image is going to open in Photoshop but if you
每当我运行这个图像时计算机 将 在Photoshop中 打开 ，但如果你
don't have Photoshop then I might just open window explore or anything like
没有Photoshop然后我可能只是 打开窗口探索或类似的东西
that but that's what's going on you also probably notice that whenever this open
但那也是你的意思 可能会注意到每当这个打开
in Photoshop look at the name in Python it was named Bucky jpg but in Photoshop
在Photoshop中查看Python中的名称 它被命名为Bucky jpg， 但在Photoshop中
it is named tum 5 a 6 a 3 b JV BMP and what this is is basically in order to
它被命名为tum 5 a 6 a 3 b JV BMP 和 这是什么，基本上是为了
open in Photoshop it needs to open a file so what pillow does whenever you call
在 Photoshop中 打开 它需要打开 一个 文件 所以无论何时打电话，枕头都能做
this show function it pretty much creates a temporary image file and it
这个节目很有用 创建一个临时图像文件和它
saves it real quick and then it opens it with whatever program that you told it
快速保存它然后打开它 无论你告诉它什么程序
to open so that is the basics and pretty much all the boring stuff of you know
打开，这是基础 和漂亮 很多你所知道的无聊的东西
the boring history of pillow some boring attributes and you know some boring
枕头的无聊历史 有些无聊 属性，你知道一些无聊
rules about open how to open it in temporary file names so now that we got all that crap out of the way we can
关于如何打开它的规则 现在，我们得到了临时文件名 所有这些废话 我们都可以
finally begin learning the cool stuff and I'm going to talk to you guys about
终于开始学习很酷的东西 我要跟你们谈谈
that stuff in the next video because I'm pretty hungry and I'm probably going to
那个东西 在下一个视频中，因为我 很饿，我可能会去
go eat like seven hot pockets right now so moving on I don't thank you guys for
现在 吃七个热口袋 所以继续我 不要 感谢你们
watching don't forget subscribe and I'll see you guys next tutorial
看着不要忘记订阅，我会 看你们 下一个教程